revv.co 2018-02-19

# Privacy Policy - Revv Fundraising Platform

Last modified: September 5, 2017

We (meaning Revv, LLC) collect certain information through our website, located at  **[revv.co](https://revv.co/)**  and/or our mobile applications, other platforms that connect to our website and/or mobile applications, and the products and services provided at our website and/or mobile applications, all as now existing or as may exist in the future (the “Platform”). This page (this “Privacy Policy”) lays out our policies and procedures surrounding the collection and handling of any information that can be directly associated with an individual, whether or not they create an account on the Platform, and includes personal information such as names, addresses, telephone numbers, email addresses, etc. (“Personal Information”).

This Privacy Policy applies only to our Platform. It does not apply to any third party site or service linked to our Platform or recommended or referred by our Platform, through our products or services, or by our staff. This Privacy Policy does not apply to any other website, product, or service operated by our company, or to any of our offline activities.

 **Personnal Information We Collect.**  We collect the following information provided from users or through user’s use of the Platform: name, e-mail address, telephone number, address, occupation, employer, employer’s address, contribution amount, contribution recipients, and credit card information. We may also collect additional information on behalf of our clients upon their request. As such, you should be aware that if a client of ours customizes information collected by the Platform, we will collect and store that information as well.

 **Non-Personal Information We May Collect.**  We may also collect information about your device type, browser, usage behavior, IP address, websites from which you came to the Platform, or websites to which you depart from the Platform. We may also collect additional information on behalf of our clients upon their request.

 **Contribution Information.**  We share information, potentially including Personal Information, concerning the contributions you make using the Platform with each candidate, committee, or organization (“Organization”) to which you made the contribution so that each Organization receiving your donations may include this information in their regulatory reports. The FEC reports containing this information are publicly available from the FEC web site. State reports are typically available through the state agency designated to oversee campaigns and elections. Often, Organizations use third parties to manage, among other things, their campaigns for contributions, including their Revv account. For purposes of this Privacy Policy, such third parties are included within the definition of “Organizations.” Organizations may receive reports about donations made through the forms they create. These reports include such items as your Personal Information and the dates, amounts, and recipients of contributions.

 **Credit Card Information.**  We outsource processing of credit card transactions to Stripe. We securely transmit your credit card information to Stripe (our payment processor). Stripe, however, does store this information. Stripe maintains that it is PCI compliant. We also store the last four digits of your credit card and the brand of the credit card. We also request your phone number and email address when you contribute so that we can reach you should further verification of your credit card information be required. Stripe uses Personal Information, including credit card information, you provide. Please visit Stripe’s privacy policy for information regarding Stripe’s collection, use, and transfer of Personal Information, currently available at  **[stripe.com/us/privacy](https://stripe.com/us/privacy)**. Please see Stripe’s security policy for additional information regarding Stripe’s security measures, currently available at  **[stripe.com/help/security](https://stripe.com/help/security).**

We request your phone number and email address when you contribute so that we can reach you should further verification of your credit card information be required. Other than the last four digits of your credit card and the brand of the credit card, Revv does not store, process, or transmit any other cardholder data in electronic format and is in compliance with SAQ A data security standards issued by the Payment Card Industry Security Standards Council.

 **Cookies and Similar Technologies.**  We use “cookies” to collect certain information from all users, including Platform visitors who complete any transaction through our Platform. A cookie is a string of data our Platform sends to your computer and then uses to identify your computer when you return to our Platform. Cookies give us usage data, such as how often you visit, where you go at the site, and what you do. We may publish such data and statistics or share such data and statistics with third parties. Please note:

  * We may also use cookies to collect email addresses of any user who visits the Platform AND we may transfer such information to third parties.
  * Our clients may independently set up cookies on products or services provided by our Platform, which may track any information that they desire to collect.
  * We also may transfer cookies and any information collected by such cookies to third parties in accordance with this Privacy Policy.
  * We may use third party analytics services that provide us information concerning your use of and interaction with the Platform. Such services include Google Analytics, MixPanel, etc.

 _Please note: You can set your web browser to refuse cookies. You can also set your browser to indicate when a cookie is being sent. The Platform may not function properly if you’ve set your browser to refuse cookies._

 **IP Addresses and Log Information.**  We log IP addresses, which are the locations of computers or networks on the Internet, and analyze them for systems administration and troubleshooting purposes. We also aggregate the number of page hits on the Platform in order to track the popularity of certain pages and improve the quality of the Platform.

 **Protection of Personal Information.**  We employ the industry standard data security tools to protect Personal Information. Unfortunately, even with these measures, we cannot guarantee the security of Personal Information. By using our Platform, you acknowledge and agree that (i) we make no guarantee as to the safety and security of your Personal Information and (ii) you use our Platform at your own risk.

 **Sharing of Information.**  Should you elect to use our Platform, we will have access to any information you provide, such as your name, address, email address, telephone number, employer, and occupation. Without limiting any of the foregoing, please note the following:

  * We may analyze this information for the purpose of providing consulting services to the Organization(s) to which you donate. The analyzed information, which may be shared with the Organization(s) to which you donate, may include your Personal Information. The individual Organization(s) to which you donate may also have access to the Personal Information you provide in the process of making a contribution by accessing its Stripe accounts. Please see the privacy policy for each Organization to which you donate for more information regarding how that Organization will collect, use, and transfer your Personal Information.
  * We may share non-personally identifiable information publicly, with our partners, and for any reason consistent with this Privacy Policy.
  * By providing your Personal Information, you are granting us the right to store and use the information in any way that does not violate any laws or regulations.
  * We also may disclose information, including Personal Information, to attorneys, collection agencies, or law enforcement authorities to address potential usage or contract violations, or illegal behavior.
  * We disclose any information demanded in a court order or otherwise required by law or to prevent imminent harm to persons or property.
  * We may share Personal Information in connection with a corporate transaction, such as a merger or sale of our company, or a sale of all or substantially all of our assets or of the product or service line you received from us, or a bankruptcy.
  * As noted above, we compile Platform usage statistics from data collected through cookies, which we may publish or share with third parties.
  * Please be aware: We may, in compliance with applicable law, convey, share, sell or otherwise transfer any of your information, including Personal Information, to third parties.

We do not control the use or disposition of your information, whether such information is Personal Information or non-Personal information, following its transmission to a third party in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Third parties to whom we transmit your information in accordance with this Privacy Policy are referred to herein as “Third Parties.” As such is the case, a Third Party may use your information in a way that is not in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Thus, by using the Platform, you consent to a Third Party’s use of your information, whether such information is Personal Information or non-Personal Information. Likewise, our Platform may link to third-party sites and third party sites may embed our Platform and/or donations forms, or otherwise link to our Platform. When using third-party sites (for example, donations sites that embed our forms), you should review the privacy policies of such third-party sites to understand how they collect and use Personal Information.

 **Information of Children.**  We understand the importance of protecting children’s privacy online. The Platform is not for use by children 13 years of age or younger. It is not our policy to intentionally collect or maintain information about anyone under the age of 13.

 **Amendment of this Privacy Policy.**  We may change this Privacy Policy at any time by posting a new version on this page or on a successor page. The new version will become effective on the date it’s posted, which will be listed at the top of the page as the new Effective Date.

 **Agreement with Privacy Policy.**  In the case that you do not agree with the way we use your information or the way that a Third Party uses your information, or any term or provision of this Privacy Policy, as now existing or as amended in the future, you may simply stop using the Platform.

 **If you have any questions concerning this Privacy Policy, please contact  [donations@revv.co](mailto:donations@revv.co)**.
